Guide to the Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records, 1970-2012.
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records,
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - Board
    - Finance Committee Meeting, January 2001 (Box 46, Folder 53)
    - Constitution & By Laws, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 2000 (Box 46, Folder 55)
    - Board Meeting, February 2000 (Box 46, Folder 56)
    - Board Meeting, May 2000 (Box 46, Folder 57)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, March 2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, February 2002 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, January 2002 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, December 2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, November 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Reports and Financials, November-December 2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, October-November 2001 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, September 2001 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, July-September 2001 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, June 2001 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, May 2001 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, April 2001 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, March 2001 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, February-March 2001 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, December 2000- January 2001 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, November-December 2000 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, October-November 2000 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, August-September 2000 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, June-August 2000 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, April 2000 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, March 2000 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, February 2000 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, Reports & Financials, December 1999 -January 2000 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - GAGV Disk with 1994-1995 Board Material, 1994-1995; FD-32 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - HIV Program, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Board Minutes, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Proposals and Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Board Minutes & Members, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Constitution, Policy, Annual Report, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Financial Statement and Annual Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Policies, 1989, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Procedures, 1989-1993 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Retreat, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Board Meeting, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Board Meeting, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - GAGV Board Meeting - Nominating Committee, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - GAGV Board Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Board, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Balance Sheets, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Board, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Financial & Legal, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Board, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Constitution, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - The Citizen Board in Voluntary Agencies, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 47)
      United Way report
    - Brochures, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - GAGV Board, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - Finance and Development Committee, 2000-2002 (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - Annual Reports, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - Tax Documentation, 1989-1990 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Congressional Directory, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Board of Directors Applications, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Board Petitions, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - Board Packets, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - Board Campaign Pledges, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - Financial Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Strategic Plan 1998-2001, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 1 of 2, 1998-2006 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 2 of 2, 1998-2006 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 1 of 2, 2010-2011 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 2 of 2, 2010-2011 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 1 of 2, 2007-2009 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 2 of 2, 2007-2009 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Financial
    - Database Project, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Picnic, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      Bills, invoices, tax documents, etc.
    - Department of Health Legislative Grant, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      Contract #M030575
    - Department of Health Tass Grant, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      Contract #C-018945
    - Anti-Violence Program Grant, 2005-2006 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      Contract #NC03896630
    - Staff Meeting, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Health Care Stabilization Grant, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Department of Health Grant, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      Contract #M010243
    - Audit, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Funding - Mainly Grants, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Application for Letter of Agreement- NY State Office of Children and Family Services, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Pride Picnic, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Budget, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Anti-Violence Program Grants, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 27)
      Contracts #C896630, #C-401198
    - Pride Picnic, July 2005 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Picnic Pre-Sale, July 2005 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Financial Statements, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 30)
      Gray Accounting report
    - Audit, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 31)
      Accounting correspondence, amortization reports, financial reports, account statements and transactions, billing
    - Department of Health Contract, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 32)
      Contract #M010253
    - Financial Statements, 2004-2006 (Box 45, Folder 33)
      Gray Accounting reports
    - Proposal for the Gay Alliance of Genesee Valley Reserve Fund, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      Prepared by Shiela Morris, Branch Manager, H&R Block Financial Advisors
    - Budget and Finance, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 35)
      Profit and Loss summaries, 2003 Annual Report, budget plan
    - Account Statements, 2001-2003 (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Financial Statements, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Financial Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 40)
      Nelson P. Maracle
    - Financial Statements, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Financial Statements, 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 43)
    - Accounting, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Tax Forms and audit correspondence
    - Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Financial Statements, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      3 copies
    - By-Laws, Undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Finances, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Financial statements, profit and loss, budget
    - Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Pamela Barres, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Banking Summaries, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      With Financial Statements
    - Financial Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - SEFA Forms, 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Personnel Policy, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Interim Audit, January-September 2004 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Financial Statements, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - NYS Department of State - Division of Corporations, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - State Contract for Building Fund, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Harry Bronson (1), 1995-1998 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Harry Bronson (2), 1994-1998 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Harry Bronson (3), 1994-1999 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Harry Bronson (4), 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      Mostly finances
    - Harry Bronson (5), 1995-1998 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      1995 NYS DIS form 497 and NYS Department of Law notices
    - NY Public Charities: Preserving Section 501(c)(3) Status, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 25)
      By Susan J. Facer, Esq.
    - Frank Novak (1), 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 26)
      Primarily finances
    - "Cards", Undated; FD-33 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - "B. Sticker Disk", Undated; FD-34 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Frank Novak (2), 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Cash Flow Management - 1995 Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Budget and Finance, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Local Law Enforcement Block Grant, February 1997 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Restricted Funds, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Personnel Policy, Undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Budget and Finance, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 33)
      Misc. Reports/Analyses/Opinions
    - Budget, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Jennifer Gaul (1), 1995-1999 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    - Jennifer Gaul (2), 1995-1999 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    - Budget, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    - Procedures Book, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Reference, 1991-1996 (Box 48, Folder 39)
    - Harlow Russell, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - "RFRN COPS 95", Undated; FD-35 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    - Resources - Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - ARI Outreach Contract, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 42)
    - 1996 and 1997 Budgets, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - GAGV Contact Information Chart, Undated (Box 48, Folder 44)
      Legal size. Found with Folder 48-26
    - Gill Foundation Workshop Participants, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Youth Program Coordinator Position Description, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Reaching Out Luncheon, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Equality Leadership Conference, October 2005 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Sweetheart Ball Forms, February 2006 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Dining Out with Friends, September 2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Finger Lakes LGTB Workforce Alliance (FLLWA) Forms, October 2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Notebook, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Member Donations, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      RESTRICTED
    - Member Donations, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Member Donations, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Member Donations, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Donor Lists, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - United Way Donors, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 34)
      marked #1135
    - United Way - Re: Donor Choice, 2001-2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - United Way SEFA, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - GAGV Financial Statements, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Fundraising, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Historical and General (1971-2007)
    - Early Photographs -NYC, Undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Lesbian Resource Center Call Logs (1), 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - National Lesbian Resource Center Call Logs, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - National Lesbian Resource Center Staff Notebook, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Lesbian Resource Center Call Logs, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Lesbian Resource Center Log, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Staff, 1977-1981 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Peer Counselor Training, 1978-1981 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - The Empty Closet - Press, c. 1977 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Financial Statements, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations, c. 1974 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Quest, c. 1974 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Cornell Gay Liberation, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Health, c. 1974 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous File, c. 1976, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Gay Parents, c. 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous HERSTORY, 1969-1974 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - City Code, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Rochester Women's Liberation, c. 1973 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1970, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Pictures -Local, c. 1973 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Local Support Statements, 1974, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Families, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Alcoholism, Undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Feminist Organizations Articles, c. 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - NGTF Support Packet, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Peer Counseling, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - GAGV Board of Directors Binder, 1975 (Box 49)
    - Coordinating Council Minutes, c. 1974 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Rochester Gay Liberation Front, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Episcopal Diocese, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Gay Liberation Voting Membership Roster and GAGV Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - GAGV Financial Statements, 1976-1978 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Library, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Answered Ad Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - GAGV Brocuhure, Undated (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - GAGV Daryl Clemens, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Conferences, Trips, Communities, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1971, 1977-1978, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Health Issues, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Community Service Organizations, c. 1983 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - LRC Bulletins, Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - GAGV News, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Program for Woman-Song and Celebration, October 11, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Flyer for Gay Prom, June 27, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - Unofficial Interests Survey, Undated (Box 49, Folder 53)
      On notecards
    - Flyer for Tea Dance, February 21, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      Battle of the Queens
    - Flyer for GAGV Auction, early 1980s (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - Card for Craftswomen, early 1980s (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - Flyer for GAGV 10th Anniversary Celebration, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - Ron Romanovsky, Paul Phillips and Nancy Vogl at Xerox Auditorium, early 1980s (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - GAGV materials, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - Empty Closet Tour and GAGV History Information, 1971-1972; 1979-1982 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - Layout Pages for Event Flyers, 1982-1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Part of the
    - Picnic Poster, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Picnic Poster, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Picnic Poster, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - LRC Referral List, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Political Organizations, c. 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Old Budgets, Financial Notes, Etc., c. 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Ledger, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Financial Monthly Statements, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - E.C Returned Billing Statements, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Financial Statements, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Kate Mullaney, GAGV Elections, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - GAGV Office Log, Undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Mary Lou Komarek, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Lesbian Publications, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Art -Music, Film, Literature, 1980, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Media, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Empty Closet Questionnaires, Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - GAGV Misc., 1977-1987 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      Lists of organizations, LGBT publications, references, books, advertisers. Monroe County Library System information. Empty Closet documents. GAGV nominations. Photograph`.
    - Religion, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - New York State Lesbian & Gay Lobby, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Lambda Update/Lambda Legal Defense & Educational Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - National Gay & Lesbian Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - New York State Division of Human Rights - Division of Human Rights, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Gay & Lesbian Advocates & Defenders Docket/Letter, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Newsletter, fundraising letter, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - ACLU - Fliers, Newsletters, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - National Coming Out Day - Invitations, Letters, Event Ideas, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - President's Report, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley Financial Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Quilt - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Lesbian Resource Center, Undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - TMAN Prog, Undated; 5" Floppy FD-40 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Write-ups for Brochure, c. 1988 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      Men's Group, Out and About, Peer Facilitators, Political Caucus, Alpha, Bridge Club, GAGV Coffeehouses
    - Form Letters, Undated (Box 50, Folder 30)
      United Way, GAGV Member Renewal, and Thank You Renewal
    - AIDS Action Plan, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - GAGV Board Training Workshop, Undated (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - EC Editor (Personnel), 1989 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - National Coming Out Week Pamphlet, Undated (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Advertising Director, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Employee Related Forms, c. 1989 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      Blank time sheets, confidentiality, self-evaluation etc.
    - GAGV Personnel Policy, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - GAGV Personnel Policy - Misc., 1993 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Incoming Letters, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence Out '90, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Corporate Documents, 1973, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - News clippings 1983-1990, c. 1983-1990 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Construction, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Memberships, c. 1988 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - TMAN Data Backup, Undated; 5" Floppy FD-39 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Membership Cards, c. 1989 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - Add to Computer Memberships, c. 1991 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - Membership Applications, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Membership Applications, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Membership Applications, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Membership Applications, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Membership Binder, 1988 (Box 34)
    - Notes - Operations, 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - Funding - ARI Contract, 1994-1997 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - Diversity Committee, 1997, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - PR Committees, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - General Correspondence (1), 1997 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - General Correspondence (2), 1996 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - Rochester General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - GAGV Constitution & By-Laws, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - GAGV Presentation Evaluation Form, Undated (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - Funding - United Way, 1996-1998 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - Pride Weekend, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - Members, Coordinators, and Organizations, Undated (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - State Grants, 1998-2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Tide Foundation, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Reporting Forms, 1999-2002 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Wilson Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Rochester Area Foundation, 1996-1998 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - S.T.O.P Grant, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - USCM Grant, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Open Meadows Foundation, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Resource Center, 1993-1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Astraea Foundation, 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1991-2002 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Funding Grants, 1995-1997 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Special Events Picnic, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Special Events Auction, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Rochester Area Task Force on Aids, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Film Festival, 1995-1997 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda, 2000-2002 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Advocacy Day, Empire State Pride Foundation - Minutes, Pamphlets (1), 2000-2003 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Advocacy Day, Empire State Pride Foundation - Minutes, Pamphlets (2), 2000-2003 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - New York State Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Minutes, Listservs, funding goals, etc., 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley - Executive Committee Meetings, Minutes, Publications, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Board Members - EC Profiles, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley - Board of Directors Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - United Way, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda Documents, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Donations, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Media Coverage, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Hairspray Tickets, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Hairspray, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Misc. Image Out, Lambda Update, Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley, 2001, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Gay Alliance of the Genesee Vallley Archives, 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Newsletters, Financial Information, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Financial Records, Annual Financial Statements, 1993, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - General Rochester/Gay Alliance of Genesee Valley, 1999, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Sweetheart Ball (1), 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Sweetheart Ball (2), 2001 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Sweetheart Ball (3), 2002 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Sub-Committee on GAGV Youth Program, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence & Email, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Logo Design, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Logo Submission, 2000; FD-41, 56 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Boy Scouts Article, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Boy Scouts Meeting, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Newsclippings, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Rochester School District, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Supreme Court Decision, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - NY Times Article, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Girl Scouts, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Budget Proposal for th Word is Out, Undated (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Community Project Surveys, 1998, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 48)
      Pride Picnic 2001 GAGV Violence Survey, 1998 Domestic Violence Survey, Speakers Bureau members
    - Boy Scouts Misc., 2001 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Important Contact Telephone Numbers, Undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Contacts, Undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - SEFA, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - SEFA, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - SEFA, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - United Way, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - United Way, 1998-2002 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Community Center Information Folder, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Policies, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Conflict of Interest and Automobile Insurance Reaffirmation form, Gill Foundation "Find the Donor" project confidentiality form, correspondence about intellectual property policy
    - Financial Statements, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Job Descriptions, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Human Resources, Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Susan - Empty Closet, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Kelly, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Strategic Plan 2002-2006 - Prep Work, c. 2001 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Domestic Partnerships, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Ad Council, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Organizational Memberships, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Grants (Information), 2002 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Policies and Procedures, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & P (1), 2000; FD-42 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & P (2), 2000; FD-43 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & P (3), 2000; FD-44 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & P (4), 2000; FD-45 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - P & P (5), 2000; FD-46 (Box 52, Folder 17)